in The Game of Life stay protected with
ICC Lombard health insurance in The Game
of Life stay protected with ICC Lombard
health insurance in The Game of Life
stay protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
insurance Game of Life stay protected
with ICC Lombard health insurance in The
Game of Life stay protected
insur in The Game of Life stay protected
with health insurance
[Music]
hello hello hello hello
hello
M hello CH hello CH hello ch
hello CH hello
ch e
[Music]
three to
smell hello hello hello hello hello CH
hello CH hello
CH br cfee
[Music]
e
e e
back
[Music]
the
hello check
check hello hello
hello
[Music]
hello e
here e
Oak
stud make a good look great with
oaksmith style Studio oaki beg it
[Music]
higher
e
e e
in The Game of Life stay protected with
IC Lombard health
insurance
e
e e
one going be distr
more out of the off to get more on the
on and gets power out
there and again he pulls
it yes this athletic
grab it's back to back ball
[Music]
of the
keeper the big pish is there
[Music]
see a big match
of
[Music]
has
by back shot of delivery and eventually
he with that wish on the
[Music]
keeper good start for
V B8 with last
one now ball goes in there with
land land it's coming from the
[Music]
back
qualifiers five towards that is that
another one yes it
is there a down in the first
[Music]
of
asking sh fish shy
[Music]
first ex of
out shot
of
SC single
SC
e
e e
disconnected e
here
spe
[Music]
by 15 as this man is indeed a Qui lap
and this time the ball is right the
where it land safely to the hands of the
down
[Music]
there Dage number two
so now it's a f damage to the Titans
and again ball goes in here
and K
Rob
so these catches are quite difficult to
get
it some was in his
eyes and quite difficult to make the
Judgment so good work at the end so over
extreme 23 of 4
again ball goes in there and it's
another damage
man
TI just at score of 23 half back and
back
[Music]
out plan
V sitting
out numers are not fing
[Music]
TI
and new man is walking
in and she a new man
and on
this number one is
on these matches out of just five
FS St
[Music]
Bing for sh
of when the sing comes
out so definitely tank
[Music]
of to come out to defend this
target
mushrooms this four rning
decision
after be F
first
in so far he has given 10s and
three and
ball in air let bit reluctant to be
sh number
23 for number four so far
and B
[Music]
in and
thatall for that
a
[Music]
his score is
26 add one that is 46
man6 overs
this SC of
the in
[Music]
second so far this man has car five
first the linan
and that was m on the side and zing in
[Music]
33 L of
six this
to to
titles that's not for
Titans and just at the score of 23
losing the seventh wicket
[Music]
and that
first the conditions the first
match this morning
[Music]
defense upon the B of the
Champions was and seems like he has
found the Gap no fer is there
[Music]
be so targ is set of 36 RS in the five
overs titles managed to got
35 say it's no man these the qualifiers
and you you know that in
[Music]
qualif let's see The Game of Life stay
protected lomard health insurance
[Music]
it all depends upon the B
Str of L sidence
[Music]
so this what it is all about to the r
and the def and let's see where this
ball pops up
[Music]
see the
don't DRS
[Music]
finals again
after
finals and finale
[Music]
76 is going to be sh the affair of this
by so just five and cter
definitely these good conditions are not
going to affect that
[Music]
[Applause]
that's
Mark in the back see
Sol a
sh and back for
[Music]
[Applause]
so f
[Music]
far IO you the capitals of the next
match
[Music]
so the
next e super Giants and Ze blasts and
the captain is com for the
toss off repeat s is coming
out since we have with the captains and
the photographer as well
[Music]
and super Jacks as we have with the
captain
[Music]
and what it
is so super job
okay
will so newer it's zoom and they have
first
[Music]
that's you
without
[Music]
damage and deliver
field
of
[Music]
f side
back to the
ball
by been without damage
[Music]
and off
it's all on the ball so this game is all
set for
[Music]
the this just five
yes this match still
long
after these two have
to is going to start the third over
comes
be
[Music]
be for
is ear for that one sh
TR
[Music]
in spint off
pass we use varation the
is STS you
[Music]
can and it's a first D and D has come
out
[Music]
a e
this mat long FR
[Music]
bus
comes
how
and how
let try to
keep will be in
the and good running by this wonderful
running
by these two last couple of first
s so it's been 24 with L of one so
becomes 12 of
[Music]
12 for
off 12 once again chion
and
[Music]
just
SP this today that becomes eight of five
[Music]
is
com seven of
[Music]
numers as the
strong s side he mo From the Block over
there
and get some the laps go
one as
r five off nine
[Music]
some stry for
this this is before the St
[Music]
s chance
and ball has
R for
that
boundary and five guns would have been
added and I
think yes VI
get this
magic
get protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with ICI Lombard health
insurance in the The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
insurance in the The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with IC Lombard health
protected in The Game of Life stay
insurance extreme BL have and we have
eled to food
[Music]
first
e
e e
[Music]
High
higher my higher my
higher higher my high my
[Music]
higher e
26 ball so far and 19
[Music]
this
slightly his fine which is number
[Music]
eight and yes he approved the shum right
at the Block on having no answer of it
I'm
[Music]
the team a good which should be will go
to the next
round with number two and three be super
e so Target sh off 24 RS
in The Game of Life stay protected with
ICC Lombard health
insurance
e
e e
to the
baller just passes
in it's a target
of 24
of
and what a good one by that shot fi
it is all the matter of the B
balls how the pressure of the open the B
balls
and putting them to do some silly
one the last B of this first over it's
been seven of one
is
[Music]
mov pressure you know that you not
having that Target so now first over
half go it's been e l one from your equ
becomes quite much in the 16 of
24 61 joury
Inda is
[Music]
how
quickly the match because it is all
about the M
of of Team having C super go to the next
round and gets his powerful one
score has reached 14
smartly B by to
see super sh that
again he has pulled it with Landing man
out of the box big
one with his b score reaches to
20 it's AIG that a shot of L and he a
for the batter this pass for big one it
has
[Music]
half be
that that be
used at the
[Music]
screen
very to get this match the scores have
Lev
[Music]
and with the single blasters get this
match and also with a convincing B of
this team and definitely it will help
them in the next
rate we having the next
match to get this it
take get this
batch rest must be happy seeing the
[Music]
DJ bra DJ bra DJ bra DJ
don't forget
with IC Lombard health insurance in The
Game of Life stay protected with ICC
Lombard health insurance in The Game of
Life stay protected with ICC Lombard
health insurance in The Game of Life
stay protected with icic Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in the game protected with ICC
Lombard health insurance in The Game of
Life stay protected with ICC Lombard
health insurance in The Game of Life
stay protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in the game of in the game of
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance health insurance in The Game
of Life stay protected with icic Lombard
health insurance in theame Game of Life
stay protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance health insurance in The Game
of Life stay
protected
e
e e
[Music]
back
no
so now sh he starts with the no
ball and license for the
batter
that
hasing comes
fore
[Music]
3 b as man back has that
out
the as inde St by the
wrestlers that's a good
come forers
[Music]
so every problem
matters thank you sir thank you so
much thank you
sir from PA and run away for the part
one by
[Music]
DJ
a and this has got the first 50 of the
day slightly yes
no as SC Empire is not interested at all
so now four it's been 50 with loss of
two wickets
[Music]
Z over s ball it's been 50
two and here the first 50 of the
B
A the loock on
finals
and the last year we seen these were
coming quite quickly but today as this
tournament has
progressed and it's getting much tougher
RS are not coming in that f
[Music]
will it be yes a good
play the damage as
will first now
[Music]
and man this time he has been the
connection
[Music]
man and it is very here to see that old
toss that was C behind
Charles as can only with the p
[Applause]
one
59 in
58 so some big hits
required it's getting tougher
something out of the box you will have
to
do as a CH plan shift the
Gars as said Ballers have become less
smart off in the first
Str yes making life difficult of the
bers
G so here ends with the sing it's been a
61 is a target
[Music]
C Lombard health insurance in The Game
of Life stay protected with ICC Lombard
health insurance in The Game of Life
stay protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with icic Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life
live e
come on
they see crew they see crew they see cre
they see
crew
e e
for this man
s he setting things apart and on the
next
ball e
start of
H superow losing Wicks back to that and
now M
bre and we it's
going for the
s slly yes no
and he ski for one
more second smart
man to the
front so fourth the
first I think it's a big
Target 57 of three
and if we talk about the catch of
session the should that was an
incredible
one yes there should be separate segment
for that spectacular
catches once again this man is very
quick look at his long
Sprint
he hold the action as you can't take
this man away from the
the soft
bounds the Feld
H than
really there
[Music]
field
position see
[Music]
attacking King Beau
footes have
captur from the
e pretty VI coming of this
tournament as could say
to who Captain with shot
[Music]
Street pretty moments of this tournament
have been captured and if you talk about
that this
tournament it has been an incredible one
by IC
[Music]
lard second this
running and go miles in the air and as
it's another Big
B on the third damage
give
the e
spe
B pass asking
is 18 on the next side
by
money that's a good call position on
this free from the
b a tough
competitor
and another damage
[Music]
Warriors
e
e e
stay protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with icic Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with ICI Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with icic Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with icic Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with icic Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with IC Lombard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with IC lomard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC lomard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC LOM lomard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC lomard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with
ICC
e
e e
[Music]
again
[Applause]
and fight
man
ball and one extra run makes him FR of
over where it
s in
fact
justs one and one extra one comes in for
extra
that this to
14 so it's all about the tempure
his emotions stre back
the ey on that
try try as it is sh right
is given to this man and he knows that
[Music]
has he sh with lot of two three balls
are left in
this hand
man go that huge one
and Maring B by
sain is's looking for the
move such
and5 as was there coming for a
movement is set all 27 round for
Vi
e
e e
dir like
Bel
[Music]
which
e
e e
and it's another one
[Applause]
man of that seon it's not the big
numbers as it
so for the passion of the sport For the
Love of the
sport and this is what team sports teach
you that it is not P being sen as
Juniors it is more
about that your your
love for this game of cricket
just
[Music]
now man
[Applause]
and there thr we are having in this
encounter it's becoming that go b m man
really W man
and yes we have got our winner Hustlers
are true
to
e e
a beautiful fact
that it's a beautiful day going ahead
and should after that break we will go
for that
quarterfinals so till then you enjoy
food Joy F along with that soft music
soft
[Music]
numers not so man because this
tournament is already wild now so go
over that high pitch encounter something
from the
DJ in the Game of Life stay protected
with IC Lombard health
insurance
e
e e
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with IC Lombard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with IC Lombard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with IC Lombard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with IC Lombard in The Game of
Life stay protected with icic Lombard
health
insurance
e
e e
now it's time for
[Music]
quarterfinals as should be huster
the TOs elect B first as in just a few
minutes canot be playing their
match as institution of the
keeper
that he of time to this fielders out
there e with counter
sh of
f Good
Feeling s BLS let jusy the name with
some Zoom
[Applause]
of the C behind at
all as I'm telling you the silen is
before the strong man
so
good is without
[Music]
damage e
having part has been very enthusiastic
now it's B
[Music]
man BL
so it's
should
been SK
up be one at second
a qu number
one and way to get off the
mark quick extension of his arm and
slicing it for a boundary
only com song please
disconnected
delivery well inside
it long appeal of behind
so is been S one and
so it's time
for this
is the the
next quarter fins out of eight encounter
and it
definitely strategies were having
different What do e
c
get it's
Mr who
fin before the STS and after the STS in
feel he's been
very enthusiastic behind the
STS keeping his teams for all high all
the p
this ENC is going to
[Music]
be enounter to body SM
[Applause]
and looking enough
f prodection is good working
[Music]
and Landing safely into the
hands of that midwicket Fielder just man
to
pocket
he F at the longent
is7 it's all about
how you
stres
this
counters and finally manages to get this
big
[Music]
one and this for the Mex
so here has
[Music]
is
not but in the
B comes from the crow and it's not a
Fielding man what an incredible save by
number seven
[Music]
suit look at over
B
A
has good
now once again cl to number
seven
has this number has something magical
number seven
[Music]
s
shooting
bounces
J
Jesus this
Qui
pass good fing again
yes is
becoming yes there is confusion the game
his on his inside the B
group his imp matches things kind small
things to could
happen the last
here only see Mr s
fromes and although his number AG might
be but as he's having a heart of a child
he is
practicing as he's just 26 the number J
is very yes he just 26 I was seeing him
he was practicing he
was spending time with this team
down
sh and has gone for the
boundary scor has
27 these kind shots
as it's a matter of
P
many fre restrictions and
other and going for that monst one
piggy comes out
with this reach to
33 and things of power quad
now see that
that matter of it's only matter of win
win win all the time
35 so this last B
left goes in there and what was that man
that was not happen won by the
fer he anticipated
completely wrong and punished with that
one
SP so that's a
good inside the P
line so
five overs
has of five
it's of the L that was
ball keep
[Music]
pretty fine going for the
p and as the strong
ising let
get and there also man of the match in
The
Knockouts as alha qu
fins not that
qual so we are having
the
match and it
really pushes the performer and along
with that other
cars and everybody wants to put
the so we the match
and that was man look at the P more like
in fashion and gets that monster flat
hit and finds a
fence power back
hit
and but this time he would
gathered What A Catch the
be coverage tring move the car
corner so easy to take on
man
for as good partnership as in progress
in of
sh on the ground
is going on in this
show
B is what a f what feeling good mind you
knew that it bounces a
lot and and a good work at the
end as SM in
Z so now 6 overs have B it's been 48
with loss of three from here projected
score seems anything around
77 so for very decent
let
keep but it hardly matters to this
man he talks in that big one over the
road and with this 50 is up for the
hustlers they reaches to
54 with that big
one 54 man big one big one
so it's a good competition is going
[Music]
between could come back
this
man his man
around to
off delivery more the
the
[Music]
and and we
it's session will have to depart
so
Falls that was for that
check
[Music]
57 here the M ball of the seven
this what
fam and
as that
willed p
if they would have El so definitely he
be sit the back out for S it's been 57
with L of
to
57 is going
away added the
fight still six are left
she TR to keep from
[Music]
the SL
be so another
Dage only one run will be added in the
total
61 16 so far still four balls
75 a very
[Music]
displine yes he moves at line
and indeed it is not
easy
to to that F
line
and that was a slight Spike and a equ
so the
damage
six only two BS in fact Three Bs coming
in this over in Fr of
white
by and this time he has sent it St into
the hands of the fielders standing at
the middle of the
so now the target is set of 62 runs it's
only three runs coming in the last
over and it that it is not that much but
defitely they
areal in the
Fielding so it's a wa for the play Party
counter definitely it is going to be one
one through blasters and
the
hustlers going to be
for so the p is set off 62 RS
[Music]
of the match from
quarterfinals Fin and and one grand
finale so the are set on two
take
e
e e
so St for that second inning starts with
that F delivery it's a target of 16
disconnected he has made in a f
for
B so good warning of these two very
quickly we have taken call F
solid punch the ball has run away with
the boundary man to the Gap he gets his
wonderful boundary look at his back
lift but Sly
punches cover
and is what a
ball what a retaliation comes from that
baller after getting the boundary it was
in the block
Hall he was looking to
it overes won by the batter and
[Music]
eventually walks out
one last part of this in first
as
it the it is also a of ball as
well for deliv comes first over is Bor
it's been eight but
still
have
F they have already played s hours
before this
rch especially
going down the leg side and it with the
for the
batter little bit wide he punishes it
more at the final and P comes
out so this
the
pressure the
enough
this tight slap
andman what an effort what an effort by
this
keeper that was a good calling by
money was a leading jge three marks The
Man Behind the stumps I tell you you see
CEO of the company but even that man
this man is giving more than
200% what a l he
is he knows that what team sport is all
about team what team matters
and
yes a huge
one it was the
SL of this right man
and right from
shot for humongous
one move his bottom hand and clean the
fence
and com
here3 20018
the next
Sixers indeed good cont
Hab comes
out see
yes that was a big one man enough time
for the battle to go for big one this
man has got such a solid body
man in
fact
his his
so next quarter it's between P super
strikers and M Warriors so it with the
captains super strikers and mother of
warriors please come for the
toss go to side s wide out there
and oh
man
delivery this man is having
[Music]
power I see
some kind
shots it's move like the
slap like you usually see the te gam
that
so just for the next and
man just before the
V right
[Music]
there hased
48 I'm sorry about that
how food there
and in the
chances top five
one second
Mo back pushed
outra and
for use
[Music]
one what a what a
this is trying up
shot so defense pass
but if we talk about the fight of
husters even
though they have play Love of
cricket in today's
play earlier they play that qualif than
that
super but the kind of commitment the
kind of predication this team that is
phenomenal
they will be the two fighters in this
tournament
Hustlers and he has pulled it where
landman gets that huge one with this we
have got our first
semi-finalist it's been do on the other
hand husters being the great
fighter so what a
match domination of
thear blasters they have
blaster in that colors man great Victory
so first finalist we are getting former
BLS
e e
in The Game of Life stay protected with
IC Lombard health
insurance e
not that but he made 39 he been unbitten
of just 12 balls and hit six
monsters six sixes came from John indura
sbad and this man became the man of the
match of this first
quarterfinals so congratulations to Z
blasters and Johnny Andora yes Johnny
yes asz he's already on
stage
and Sh power you crash over
completely getting
Beau
organizers so full marks to organizers
as well as for the tournament they have
Oran nied such an
incredible and indeed
having great time in this
tournament there happy faces all
around greatting
action so now it's time for the second
match second
final Strikers and
Mar
forious
e
e e
disconnected e
e
e e
as move for
and that was a switch
attempted more like Maxim fashion who
for that monster
one and huge one has come
out as of
Warriors the first experience six so far
that's
and is what a effort
man mon his man so get
short
great
close certainly easy to
see it's in a difficult
position tring like 4 towards him
and yes just going with the p of the
ball with more pick up shot
and take to 199 one and did a first
over so after the first quickly M
Warriors manes to get 19 R good in the
first
over so indeed it's a good start by The
Warriors
now it's time for
[Music]
S as it's been already 19 RS in the
first
over left and combination right in
strong let's
see just guiding it
man
have found God beautiful be
in the direction of the in
[Music]
the strong man is more
looking the fence
of a
spot and this will
takish ball has run towards the fence
and B becomes on
man so the to the
[Music]
comes hard for that kind of so comes
really hard if ball gets Edge so
definitely it
will five
more and the distance and K this man Tes
to for that switch hook and a it with
that
boundary it's a partnership of 31 run
between anit and
Krishna reaches to 31 the exact number
which s is
[Music]
wiing and as
so good wi this over two overs having
goal and the score is exact the number
of Joi
[Music]
going around 16
CH as
BR yes it is
has been his first
just and where it
flies as this ball just to the
kabin
went really high and exactly the
distance
37 a St from the
Warriors
first very
quickly
and man you can't do such kind of simple
Mons
for
and
these in this
[Music]
SC it is
what what great
fing has good
M able to get it so
just
to another
guy coming previous
over intensity of this
tournament 307
see the F
number that's SM
knows his line very
[Music]
good P of the
hands one of the
best so
just trying to keep
the and now it has been
cented as he trying to keep it away from
the B but eventually came on the WR side
and what a put by
this his
b and
again
boss and this man know very well this
kind of
delance to back and now this partnership
has SC 54 RS
so is getting a good
St really
over
open 15
that's
go and
[Music]
again over appeal four it's been 54 with
L of one
so this will be L the of K
this
has good partnership
[Music]
has been
with he has advantage of context
[Music]
B he had noticed it earlier he's coming
to the track just for that short
one so qu is going
and K man and this time the ball has
found some part of the bats here into
the hands of the keeper to Second damage
after that couple of B now exp 54 and
second to get down
here so SM
man
he was F SP
will discipline on his
L slightly Chang with length and being
gifted with
the just have the score of in The Game
of Life stay protected with ICC Lombard
health insurance
this
SL has go to 50 this fth
that's got soft
push
chastic with the blue
JY and that was
[Music]
side has some
good to
161 and again man he has gone for that
huge one so 1 runs and a wicket keep in
the
super so 5 over it's 67 with lot of two
wickets
spe
man should way
a so slightly longer bound right
there so going for the big
one it's matter of
ball these are eight
cter time we talk about
that at the same time if comes it always
that which really advantage to the ball
inside that is a
because in especially short performance
in five for or
spe
67 SC down the L
to shot the man
SM
by
has great f
[Music]
just just to the with that
power and even go well through so it
hits
[Music]
the POS frustration
of and now the next ball gets that
wicket
[Music]
so the
fouret has been falling so 6 over 7 it's
73 with L of
four and triple
digit and
left so left up with that 28 BS 28
BS that triple digit
Mark is 72
a very enthusiastic Camp of super
strikers was a Shar one
is having a good control on his L and
L no prodction
[Music]
there game with the call box
so St in B and C3 in the hands of Sudan
so good composure if this team is
showing with a good come back on very
next play Pi
[Music]
by it's been caught he the short cover a
time this is a second wiet
the back ball has towards the
finion so between ball and back
10 comes out he looking more clear the
school
Legion just tou to the CL and
[Music]
good
positions intelligent
candidate
and right out of the
bar so now ends with the single it's
been 81 with loss of five at s overs and
with this four is also
ready and so teams who are present out
here of guest please enjoy
the so by life
f as it is not about only the cricket
it's everything is wonderful in this
tournament IC
[Music]
League 2035 first
edition of this
tournament and I hope in once we will
have a lot
of lot of of tournament from ICC
Lombard and what start
is that for the
timeout
e
e e
sever overs have it's been
E55 and see
everything have this
out as we can
understand it's the heat of this
tournament as this tournament is
progressing as it's getting more intense
it's more competitive and it's what a
fing effort man what a fing effort you
he manages to get the
boundary
Andes
to to number
[Music]
so and
attention under
86 and
Def
Advantage a short of and on great fing
man
so
this and as 87 two balls are left in
this first
ining Stu K is on
and once again this ball is high K crew
goes for that big
one it's really got a great elevation
[Music]
93 and this inning keeps it smartly by K
so Target of
94 they have got a good
Target and let's see how
Strikers make a shoes of this big one
his Warriors putting down humongous Tav
has getting good
Advantage the one CH
definitely they have good
cushion of such
a so it is going to be a m b once again
this Leal encounter between Warriors and
super and just before we have already
had a
but exchange
between in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance
e
e e
and from that full and
deliv that's friend
here and is what a
shot it's not easy to be these touches
and signant man and gets a b
match toch quarter semi or a final
it's been without any damage
here man making full use of the power
play just before the B
go and a good at this
[Music]
it is very important that how
they how they
use these two B
PS and is good catch man good catch by
the telling you it's not easy to be he
got of catches
the first
play and at
least that at
least okay
and it once
[Music]
again once again wonderful catch
these sun is
eyes end the damage to super
strikers for
shot for
that's good look at the short cover
is that
one the
has a score 74
RS one is left in
[Music]
this the last of the second
B equation becomes 76 of
is
[Music]
13 x 18 with
ofs e
that job give the tobacco
[Music]
and not giving enough for the
shs this
this it's k
Le has been in the
Bing ww
Warriors so we have next match here
between wbwe Warriors and policy Bazar I
request both the captains please come at
the scoring area for the
toss so next match is the
between
[Music]
wtw war and
policy and so he know his SP very well
all the
deliveries need in of that of that
b good is going
on
have coming in from a 5 by three the
B as inde this is given tough to the
B the
SP of this
[Music]
third
five not coming from the seet
SP he has to be Happ the so
now6 three
overs left
for ers
that's 68 of
30 go
14 the field
so lose of the match
between for the next match
and warriors here Bazar the toss and C
for the Fielding
first and what a shot man what a shot
just walked over
and for huge
[Music]
one
to and he was to mind on but even then
he manages to get this
boundary smly B by him that he was
walking down the track and
just even then Kash man get this
B good come back
kishna production
R away yes it
is so the7 it has reach
41 so could over for Super
cers and slightly de in the 100 as well
the Le
join around
[Music]
13 as at pleas of two
def in every
over
for1 and he become SC 53 of 24
this
next it has travel
just couple of
FS so it's a smart by
[Music]
is easy for the
so far in the first four balls
going with that fly
so Three G the bigest
over
[Music]
44 and
now they have 18 BS left and now it
becomes a task of 51
runs e
for
he really exting things
and now this time he has B
man that
so reaches to 45 the sixth over is
running asking goes to 19 right now
there oneing man what a
finging three for his
team all for the
boundary has clean
work 45 out there
[Music]
this is of the
over
1847 the of the Warriors having
making a b
cless
[Music]
47 and Co back all the bman this got a
short
one the of the
B
connected C
behind
keeping behind but no impr
53 and that
walk a tennis B destrction man goes for
that extra B for the power
as
behind
this for that big but and What A Catch
What A
Catch finally being picked
out so it's the damage for super
strikers
now there is one thing that can see
them need of
it's a l be
so now over it's been six L of and the
last over there a need of only
B see 34 on short having only six balls
how schol are than
[Music]
got
e
e e
Lombard health insurance in The Game of
Life stay protected with ICC Lombard
health
insurance
so first we
congratulate second semi-finalist mother
Warriors the two semifinals and now it's
time for the man of the
match of the current match that goes to
unle such an Ord performance by this
man his balling he gave nine R in his
two and back three wickets along with
that his batting such as tendous
performance by this man with 47 of 18
two4 and
sixes so congratulations to Mother
Warriors and an so please come at
the stage to pick your beautiful tropy
of the man of the
match so such a great performance will
be shown by Mar Warriors a dominant one
and now move to the another
round and now next match we are having
between policy and wtw
warriors here Bazar Ste go for the fing
first e
in The Game of Life stay protected with
ICC Lombard health insurance in The Game
of Life stay protected with ICC Lombard
health insurance in The Game of Life
stay protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with
IC
e
e e
spe
yes it's the first s to W
Warriors it's a FL delivery of
this just the SCH of six
there and this match is a KCK to the
semi-finals is having to the
back as look at the last
off is the very
F in
Feld charge on the
forers see to wait for them passing
in that
was from the P so the runs will will not
be
confed
so
comes one left as there is confusion is
gone
and goes to
sh although was Ring quite quickly
towards
him soen after the party last night I
man
happen say of the party that c of
catches IND good H man so here is a
seven of one at the first
over and T is at
five Shan is at
one comes to the second of the ining
St the
talk I wonder they had the spongy B was
there
let be S human
short
[Music]
cover it might give some kind of
advantage to the B
but right
now you can see
how is going in the air
of the
co about the
fly 12
RS that was block
all good single has been sneaked
the second is all to the last ball of
the
second and this time takes enough
elevation and huge one comes toer so it
goes to 19 L one add of two overs
is who end this over although he got
some advantage of the be
play that was not prob for the
backand it but manages to get that
one is going to strong the of this third
over
[Music]
Curr fore
in that's that was not easy to play on
as his
peace he his fingers on the
so far in first
BS this is also having the advantage of
his of his
height sh in the production on the
soy with
[Music]
this
sh he has good this over only three came
in the third over
[Music]
22 and espe if you talk about this
tournament the way that has
organized so all course to the organiz
[Music]
tournament to the
show in climax of this
tourament look at the
enthusiasm in the
teams teams which participated in this
tournament
so is
from great love for this tour the have
sh all
participated
c as is here and that got FL picks it
for the p
as as it of left
SE the name
of these names comes when we talk about
the left and seers
finishes pretty
well although this guy is witing Good
Feeling short
cover
as is waiting that is also of the fin SE
number
9 how
this do some fun
things for
so the fin comes out that a
TOA with the B and
protection for the single so good over
here here four overs B it's been 30 with
loss of one
so entrance game in the previous
[Music]
over as
this with one
and
again is the first
one he gave
the for the
B
fore speeech
[Music]
score 35 the
toone we looking for that third
semi-finalist after this mat we s
having four
matches
that muched game which we are
waiting for such a long time that grand
finale so will be to to
that
we
the
Hees a
b after that getting that b for the
first ball come back
and even though that
was good come back but good come back by
the B as
well after that b smashes his father
pick
one and this ball has gone in air
and man it has been
dropped so this t ball bounces a
lot but not so difficult
one this
SK an easy one it's been 44 one and five
r
44 projected score seems anything
[Music]
round 7375
what
so something things time easy for them
out
[Music]
there qu
of cantic
[Music]
BL discipline principl are
this
is they are looking to for the
oppent that's pretty on this
ball that chance for the
[Music]
ball but
at pretty in good com
the the situation came on this back was
given by
the AL the it might
for in I you it's not when the in his
for to save to make such kind of
saves on the 50 is only for the
waras has still that 14 balls they have
finished
15 as something we have observe as this
tournament is progressing it's getting
really tough for the B to score ons it
goes more the fing with the
body so this is part of a
good because the most toughest part that
is a fiing the most of his
part being in the
field and the kind of efforts which that
fast ball is B
so the single game of the last part of
this over it's been 52 or one add six
overs
e
e e
in The Game of Life stay protected with
ICC Lombard health
insurance
e
e e
that was a boss
in
good the action of this
match and things are getting quite right
now but it
happen this is kind
of small coulden
and is what a sh
man short and back
right
there he himself to go from sh
is the a thi out footage on the
production on the first slip
yes indeed he's a very smart
candidate all the time he keeps putting
his fingers on the
ball and look at it
man a huge one enough with was given and
especially this shot is not easy to be
on when
you have to make that extension of his
arm and find the WID more like the
cion more like
her get the
friends
to that is more back
that's at the last moment hisus and one
extra as f
[Music]
and
yes
but dece the backwards an incredible
Feeling by
sh
call and this man with his quick
fuit keep
[Music]
second
exper
to again SP
sh
this battle
this time better be no mistake and clear
for the huge one
man
7 still three balls are
left so
far
for come back
by
deliv look at this
guy he seems like that it's more like
he's old man getting more intoxicated
this time
not from the last
qu
[Music]
still still
left in this first in already they have
got a
good so could 20 finish 20 of this first
inning
79 Target
get SS
of so War put in a
people and P for that senstive fight
between and WW
Warriors in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance
e
e e
that's up small one
[Music]
andov the
the
king
how could
be that life to
that the P SM B
so it's been without any damage it's a
task of
and that go on the
PS and this man is having enough power
enough time to do such kind of TRS
and again man back to back
[Music]
bful toss and went for that huge one
man yes you can't give chance to this
man strong but slight collusion
but after
that off
[Music]
79 that's
as
wonderfully
the just keep this time and this time it
has gone through the Gap to the camera
person and goes for that poy two F the
chase but immense power was behind that
sh
and and get out
one with the
power Tak the
[Music]
33 first
two 33 and from here it is still
a big tower of
inds I tell you it's not easy to play
with this time ball when you used to
that left
ball as it takes time to the s
some extra bounds SM bounds is small in
size and and What A Catch man what a
catch that's a great catch he has taken
it and here the flause all in the pass
[Music]
he mind
but kept the school and that F
that
c so now first
SP power
off and indeed this cor of Fielding
has C some momentum
shift comes with the F delivery the
block soly this is
weting that when this kind of fiing
happens so energy fling down it
can test of your
temperament you know that it's a big
game quarterfinals around
of the P he moves there a huge graap and
gets it
bound SM he know that of the
gaps with this
gaps he go
didn't manage it doesn't matter to get
that much
off but bre l so definitely be Gap so
now squ go more
[Music]
deeper m bound once
again and
that all fing that shot and
[Music]
change
of 4 and
and PR once again
question com to 38
29 so important how many
[Music]
two and once again man this man is in
picture again this is wonderful C the
second blue
indeed we
Wasing more vision of M
that's got good
F has been just a
while but kept an eye on his ball and
then once again good Fielding
the count off the
JY coming from the suit
SP
this back
than
could it's a good
[Music]
contest
and fi deep the F leg and P becomes up
part the
bank
from with this to reaches to 47 F there
ex of 33 runs
good this the B with his St just push
him down see the
B
47 with L of two contes going between B
and
it's a third quarterfinal only we have
two
semifinalist for epod
one with the number of M number 10
in this
face see go
in the air even though getting them prop
on the B but enough strength this man is
having it has gone we B the for that
one it's been a 50 up of policy
Bazar and that one has also man
54 Where Ram contribution with 50 runs
man and with this takes a total to 60
man what a what a strength this guy is
having immense strength this big Muslim
man people has reach
60 that 50 is
running it's all the
ball again
[Music]
that's what far Works coming from the
stall L all the time he's talking in big
on in big numbers this big gu
talks to 66 from here to 14
guns the
cash that was Dro a for on just second
round and coming down the
track and now you can't stop this
one he is
Unstoppable and all the Fe power yes
it's a hean show I'm hearing that it's a
e
man to do as he looks like out and
number number
12 it's been 72 with L of two shot
from of seven rounds
inside the
line and
finally it's a big wick
of super
from
the
once she power he showed his she power
in this
tournament now there is a of
ss let's see what is called this key of
the Warriors right now
and sing 15
balls as it's a matter of ball balls all
the time it's a matter of ball
balls if you look the
chances in this shter format so
[Music]
so to
75 ball is left in the sixth over
the second in
this the second has well the need five
FS at this match while having 12
balls so it's been all matter off for B
balls and how
smartly
uses next two
overs e
and the support comes
that's lead of five runs having 11
balls so is all about what PR field
position which guys is
batting comes
is
here this game not in the last but
a of four that caugh behind pushes the
PA still two balls left in this
over so far only two
RS the ball has run toward the boundary
comes for the couple
[Music]
of SC
79 and look at the relax of policy
[Music]
Bazar be
rela
through and clears it and with this big
one Tak this match in and we are getting
here yes the third finalist the third
semifinalist of this tournament policy
Bazar so yes
congratulations to the
teams all the teams who are
participating in this tournament as
making this tournament wonderful and now
happy congratulations to Paar and a
great fight sh by wpw Warriors put good
put on board and that was a chance which
came came to them in that second ball
that was a catch of Raman which was St
and then he gave life to such kind
of little B so it in The Game of Life
stay protected with ICC Lombard Health
Insurance Lombard health insurance in
The Game of Life stay protected with ICC
Lombard health insurance in The Game of
Life stay protected with ICC Lombard
health insurance in The Game of Life
stay protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with IC lomard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with ICC LOM health insurance
in The Game of Life stay protected with
ICC Lombard health insurance in The Game
of Life stay protected with ICC Lombard
health insurance in The Game of Life
stay protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with ICC LOM lomard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC I Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with icic Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with IC Lombard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with IC Lombard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with icic Lombard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with IC Lombard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
insurance
e
e e
is it yes no
noer before
the is that yes or
[Music]
no it looks like
sh the
F SC
and I don't know what this man is having
love with this com
box yes the second shot in just in the
SP of this 78 balls consider com BS
man he's not like the comment at the
[Music]
broadcasting it's been e without any
damage so far second
spe
so7 it's been 19 without any
[Music]
damage
for for for
[Music]
and Well
Done play with some see this
p and
fore
and slightly difficult Cho
that
man need
to check that what exactly has happen
almost he had C that
ball this
pass inside the vi just the
[Music]
that's what a
catch good catch by I tell you these
catches are
be
[Music]
as
he has good control on his hand
and first play the opening
with that so it's been 241 add three
overs
again this time
New
Zealand champion newal
that coming for the 2way
for
and here it has
gone need the banner and huge run
huge comes
[Music]
out passion for this game
team has organized this tournament and
at the same time they're
participating mon to all the
time
whether to see the facilities which they
have in this T and along the time the
of
show as we have already got three fin so
who with the 4 to one in these
two F
delivery and Big
B with the this man right under the back
he loses AAS
to find the spot and long Deion comes
out
[Music]
as us is present for one and one G good
fiing shot
and yes just at the com the third shot
go to the coms
man
M although it's not coming pop to the
backat he's mising this shot but the
distance this shot has covered the great
one
scor
to couple of f has scored two at the
end so
[Music]
here
here so this a huge one it's
54 and got
it it almost
[Music]
got so and one team is getting
200% but this time
he and so you can't SK out from the
hands of
sun very
first and this catch was also not so
easy one keeping his schol and giv
so five overs having it's been 54 of two
wickets
the
monst that's monster
H look at the
back and this guy know the Str
and that 8 has to
pick
16 28
that SC theer is in the
choice at the end this ball is going to
the for this 10 coming in speed two
[Music]
balls at the
C Mar smashes is highly motivated
as the captain of M
is has to he keep push team on the
time exp on the
field or out the
bre full delivery you Ball s of to this
man with with this
space already
7s still the last one of this over
[Music]
find previous over it's been 712 and six
overs
[Music]
here
71 f
ex
situation he's a he's got a good
[Music]
control his pleas
was good here
he will one simple chances dropped in
this over
he keeping
tight not
forth a
TOs and this time this SL the
St so whether the Fielding or the
balling all the time this man is the
reaction earlier he took wonderful catch
wiet belongs to him that was a drop in
that P4 and this time collecting it
and making the Tello Smashers to three
down at the score of
[Music]
75 in
has he
76 the last of the same
coming
the
first the
once the
game maximum shots coming toward com
[Music]
box3 with that good one
good come
[Music]
back and again goes for the big one
takes to 89 and it's
a 50 for an lead to 53 what a knock of
of the
25 has
53 and
again it's all the
time big big number
last
that's making for
himself Ando ends to the boundary here
big Target set for one one that is 100
runs it's a huge
Target Mar speci set for one team it's
one so we see what is going to be happen
in the second inning
that's e
health insurance in The Game of Life
stay protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with icca Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with IC Lombard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with icca Lombard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with IC Lombard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with IC Lombard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
insurance in The Game of Life stay in
The Game of Life stay protected with ICC
Lombard health insurance
protected with ICI Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with icic Lombard health
insurance in the game of
e
e e
have
ball has
the so first over has it's been F
without any damage
[Music]
a big task off one
runs and then first over ites four
New Zealand GJ
and it has gone and What A
Catch What A
Catch he was trying to judge it and
eventually e
com
pleas how with this match up
[Music]
so Curr second over
starting it's reaching just six
Bo and more Closs
and he what a Fielding effort man what a
Fielding
effort look at the high spirited camp
[Music]
and that
was not came for the bad so now two7
it's been 10 with
one and left Target of one
so
far to far
[Music]
is going pretty high he
has to 15 R
over has come for the third
over side
High
[Music]
guy
second so far
already go
[Music]
the has two
backups working G
so for this match there is update from
indiaand match India has lost three
Wicket just at the score of 51 in 15
overs and that J is the same
Smashers have been in this match
spe so runners in this over along with
that
making the
connection yes s of shots
required required
[Music]
third is running G
Tas of 81
runs he's having five fors
muched B has come
know
shot of L and going for more squish
boundary that huge one comes
out there flat
six this kind of
from ex a big task left Downs
the enas leader of mar
measures just keep pushing his guys as
he knew that his back up his
[Applause]
[Music]
first move on the p and eventually be
picked out at the sco
L so the damage but it looks like
the further F the situation that
one over and it's 31 with loss of
three so it's a task of
69 of
24 goes to anything around
17 just will send in right now
thead and has 41
out
each
got
far
shot you will have to take
chances against some good
you have
some attack in the
body let see we the chances against
against of
4 to
14 for 60 runs now having 20 balls
for
himself that good f
overed five over 7 it's been 42 with
loss of
three from the CER you can hear the loud
voice of
prot the offn of my smes
put that short FL
is a non Striker
in
and we are about to CL with just four
team will qualify for the
semifinals has been a great contest
among all the team the teams having
these qualifi and quarterfinal
[Music]
spirited keeper of
mar so six SC have 47 of three wickets
for
e
e e
St
so is going
on coming this first fours
make
sure my God
s over7 more F coming in this previous
over it has reached to 52 with loss of
three has
so now it's the toss time for the
semifinal number
one yes only last over is
left in this quarterfinal
match and quarter and sages are about to
finish and now we are going for that
semifinal number one that's between
mother Warriors and policy
Bazar we just three mag shot of the of
that Pro
[Music]
Fact Two s and one final so first semi
is s between m b and polic has
captains pleas up the scoring area for
the
toss
[Music]
CL see
comes coming from Mar special
ch
last of
this
finalist still the name of the thir
final
and comes
out the
finals hello so finally we have got a
war last but not the least quter final
[Music]
so Mar smash through to
semifinals
conspir team one one
team could s throughout in this
tournament and will be the organizers
as here is the
photographer how should go and take some
pictures come and some pictures
man sry
life stay protected with ICC Lombard
health insurance in The Game of Life
stay protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected in The Game of Life stay
insurance
e
e e
hello hello
some here smart adoption for that
sh going
on 12 have come in this
first as well with the line
en e
in The Game of Life stay protected with
ICC Lombard health
insurance
e e
back is
required happen the match this
tournament is way closer
and he has been that scol where it goes
with a good effort use his L
hand
and
e
e e
for
warriors and one more back
hi
e
e e
in The Game of Life stay PR protected
with ICC Lombard health
insurance
e
e e
in The Game of Life stay protected with
ICC Lombard health
insurance
e
e e
in The Game of Life stay protected with
ICC Lombard health insurance in The Game
of Life stay protected with ICC Lombard
health insurance in The Game of Life
stay protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC I Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with icic Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protect
e
e e
with icic Lombard health insurance
in The Game of Life stay protected with
ICC Lombard health insurance in The Game
of Life stay protected with ICC Lombard
health insurance in The Game of Life
stay protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with IC Lombard health
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance Insurance in The Game of Life
stay protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
Insurance in The Game of Life stay
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
insance Insurance in The Game of Life
stay protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance in
the
e
e e
Dage the chance B
first
first has some different kind
[Music]
and fr four 16 without any damage
they see crew they see crew they see
crew they
[Music]
cre e
this some
different the first
you can't do you see you can't get this
of
[Music]
I that's again that's
again again that's again
[Applause]
[Music]
and C that solid
connection for that big one
[Music]
again
man as with that huge one it takes a
total 239 in just two overs
[Music]
spee fore
has
in good one
[Music]
and look at
it what a
[Music]
more like the tight slab more on the on
side and this partnership goes to1 of
just 14 balls open S policy Bazar
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
doctors and man what a
shot flogging in his own
fashion like he had enough time to play
the
shot pleas and this passes it for that
see for this one
B in the air and with a huge
distance not only that's
elevation but along with that go such a
big distance
other
new one is
the to
sh
that fin he's take back
me me
e
e e
the
[Music]
love side
C Camp
ofing
[Music]
all and again it happens with
that's has been missed out by himself
[Music]
I think that swi
it and he has gone for the
boundary to
98 two shot
[Music]
hey hey they cre cre cre
the
fers F out 30 yard
[Music]
the total has reached
99 last one of
this and with this white it's 100 of
football
[Music]
Bazar and finally finds his
Wick 5 over 00
first
this first of 11
to one
L of two
wickets 58 of
[Music]
16 to
block
for
e
e e
s over it's 113
this is a l
work the big
one
e e
again
[Music]
again about
the target is of 125
RS total
with icic Lombard health insurance in
The Game of Life stay protected with ICC
Lombard health insurance in The Game of
Life stay protected with ICC Lombard
health insurance in The Game of Life in
The Game of Life stay protected with ICC
Lombard health insurance in The Game of
Life stay protected with ICC Lombard
health insurance in The Game of Life
stay protected with IC Lombard health
insurance in The Game of Life stay
protected with ICC Lombard health
insurance
e
[Music]